so let's see if we can correctly use
msync
let's say that we have a processor with
a very relaxed consistency model where
all four reorderings are allowed
including reordering writes to different
locations on a core let's say that this
is the code we are executing we do a
load link of lock into r1 we then do a
branch
if we didn't get the lock back to
checking
we do a store conditional
trying to now get the lock we loop back
if we didn't get the lock
then we load the variable increment it
and store it and then we free the lock
by writing zero to it
so the question for you
is where do we need msync if anywhere
here
do we need one
do we need one here do we need one here
here
how about here
how about here and how about
at the end
of everything